Ceremonies and Events Office fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Convocation files, 2015; 1967-2023; F-91-3; 1.69 m of textual records
  - Convocation Fall 2020 (3 volumes), F-91-3-0-0-96
    Due to COVID-19, SFU did not hold an in-person Convocation ceremony for Fall 2020. In addition to the Convocation book, this file includes the package of materials students were sent, including pins, a cap and box.
    Textual records; Artefacts
    - SFU Fall 2020 Convocation, F-91-3-0-0-96-1
  - Convocation, Spring 2021, F-91-3-0-0-97 (Archival box - standard 91-31)
    Due to COVID-19, SFU did not hold an in-person Convocation for Spring 2021.
    Open, no restrictions
    - SFU Spring 2021 Convocation book
  - Convocation, Fall 2021, F-91-3-0-0-98 (Archival box - standard 91-31)
    - SFU Fall 2021 Convocation book
  - Convocation, Spring 2022, F-91-3-0-0-99 (Archival box - standard 91-31)
    - SFU Spring 2022 Convocation book
  - Convocation, Fall 2022, F-91-3-0-0-100 (Archival box - standard 91-31)
    - SFU Fall 2022 Convocation book
  - Convocation, Spring 2023, F-91-3-0-0-101 (Archival box - standard 91-31)
    - SFU Spring 2023 Convocation book
  - Convocation, Fall 2023, F-91-3-0-0-102 (Archival box - standard 91-31)
    - SFU Fall 2023 Convocation book
- General ceremonies and events files, 1965 - 1994; F-91-4; 64 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to a variety of ceremonies and events organized by the Ceremonies Office. Activities documented include dinners, receptions, memorial services, exhibitions and other special occasions held to honor students, staff, faculty, alumni, and distinguished visitors. Records include programs, invitations, guest lists, books of words (order of proceedings), correspondence, notes, publications, brochures, and other documents.
  - BC Scottish Festival, 1982; F-91-4-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 91-13)
  - Business Administration Ceremonies Committee, 1982; F-91-4-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 91-13)
  - Faculty and staff retirement dinner, 1982; F-91-4-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 91-13)
  - Stephen Hinchcliffe memorial service, 1982; F-91-4-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 91-13)
  - Ted Sinnott plaque unveiling, 1982; F-91-4-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 91-13)
  - An afternoon of visual arts - The Native Sons of B.C., 1983; F-91-4-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 91-13)
  - Dinner for Ivany and Saywell / Cotes reception for Saywell, 1983; F-91-4-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 91-13)
  - Display - letters patent, 1983; F-91-4-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 91-13)
  - Miscellaneous events, 1983; F-91-4-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 91-13)
  - Miscellaneous events, 1983 - 1984; F-91-4-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 91-13)
  - Board retirement dinner, 1984; F-91-4-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 91-13)
  - Miscellaneous events, 1984; F-91-4-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 91-13)
  - Reception for Harry Evans, 1984; F-91-4-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 91-13)
  - Reception for Olympic athletes, 1984; F-91-4-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 91-13)
  - Faculty and staff retirement dinner, 1984; F-91-4-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 91-13)
  - Miscellaneous events, 1985; F-91-4-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 91-13)
  - Nehru exhibition, 1985; F-91-4-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 91-13)
  - Shrum memorial service, 1985; F-91-4-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 91-13)
    Restricted in part
  - Miscellaneous events, 1986; F-91-4-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 91-13)
  - President's Club dinner, 1986; F-91-4-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 91-13)
  - Reception - Woodward Chair and tenth anniversary of Women's Studies program, 1986; F-91-4-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 91-13)
  - Faculty and staff retirement reception, 1986; F-91-4-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 91-13)
  - Shrum book party, 1986; F-91-4-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 91-13)
  - Shrum Scholars reception, 1986; F-91-4-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 91-14)
  - Miscellaneous events, 1987; F-91-4-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 91-14)
  - President's Club dinner, 1987; F-91-4-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 91-14)
  - Faculty and staff retirement reception, 1987; F-91-4-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 91-14)
  - Women's Studies Reception - Woodward Chair, 1987; F-91-4-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 91-14)
  - Miscellaneous events, 1988; F-91-4-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 91-14)
  - President's Club dinner, 1988; F-91-4-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 91-14)
  - Miscellaneous events, 1989; F-91-4-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 91-14)
  - President's Club dinner, 1989; F-91-4-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 91-14)
  - Reception - 25th Anniversary Committee, 1989; F-91-4-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 91-14)
  - Faculty and staff retirement reception, 1989; F-91-4-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 91-14)
  - Thelma Finlayson Society (donors) dinner, 1989; F-91-4-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 91-14)
  - Dean's reception - certificate and diploma ceremony, 1989 - 1990; F-91-4-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 91-14)
  - George Halpern memorial service, 1990; F-91-4-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 91-14)
  - Board of Trade governor's banquet, 1990; F-91-4-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 91-14)
  - Thelma Finlyson Society reception, 1990; F-91-4-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 91-14)
  - J. S. Woodsworth Chair, 1990; F-91-4-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 91-14)
  - Miscellaneous events, 1990; F-91-4-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 91-14)
  - President's Club dinner, 1990; F-91-4-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 91-14)
  - Miscellaneous events, 1990 - 1991; F-91-4-0-0-43 (Archival box - standard 91-15)
  - Faculty and staff retirement reception, 1990; F-91-4-0-0-44 (Archival box - standard 91-15)
  - Twenty-five year employee reception, 1990; F-91-4-0-0-45 (Archival box - standard 91-15)
  - Thailand Princess visit, 1990 - 1991; F-91-4-0-0-46 (Archival box - standard 91-15)
  - Convocation - University College of the Cariboo, 1991; F-91-4-0-0-47 (Archival box - standard 91-15)
  - Dean's reception - certificate and diploma ceremony, 1991; F-91-4-0-0-48 (Archival box - standard 91-15)
  - Thelma Finlayson Society reception, 1991; F-91-4-0-0-49 (Archival box - standard 91-15)
  - President's Club dinner, 1991; F-91-4-0-0-50 (Archival box - standard 91-15)
  - Faculty and staff retirement reception, 1991; F-91-4-0-0-51 (Archival box - standard 91-15)
  - Twenty-five year employee reception, 1991; F-91-4-0-0-52 (Archival box - standard 91-15)
  - Hong Kong alumni dinner, vol. 1, 1991 - 1992; F-91-4-0-0-53 (Archival box - standard 91-15)
  - Hong Kong alumni dinner, vol. 2, 1991 - 1992; F-91-4-0-0-54 (Archival box - standard 91-15)
  - Hong Kong alumni dinner, vol. 3, 1991 - 1992; F-91-4-0-0-55 (Archival box - standard 91-15)
  - Dean's reception - certificate and diploma ceremony, 1992; F-91-4-0-0-56 (Archival box - standard 91-15)
  - Thelma Finlayson Society reception, 1992; F-91-4-0-0-57 (Archival box - standard 91-15)
  - Founders and friends reception, 1992; F-91-4-0-0-58 (Archival box - standard 91-15)
  - Miscellaneous events, 1992; F-91-4-0-0-59 (Archival box - standard 91-15)
  - President's Club dinner, 1992; F-91-4-0-0-60 (Archival box - standard 91-16)
  - Faculty and staff retirement reception, 1992; F-91-4-0-0-61 (Archival box - standard 91-16)
  - Twenty-five year employee reception, 1992; F-91-4-0-0-62 (Archival box - standard 91-16)
  - Convocation - University College of the Cariboo, 1992 - 1993; F-91-4-0-0-63 (Archival box - standard 91-16)
  - Donna Laws luncheon and farewell reception, 1993; F-91-4-0-0-64 (Archival box - standard 91-16)
  - Thelma Finlayson Society reception, 1993; F-91-4-0-0-65 (Archival box - standard 91-16)
  - Miscellaneous events, 1993; F-91-4-0-0-66 (Archival box - standard 91-16)
  - President's Club dinner, 1993; F-91-4-0-0-67 (Archival box - standard 91-16)
  - Faculty and staff retirement reception, 1993; F-91-4-0-0-68 (Archival box - standard 91-16)
  - Saywell's farewell dinner, 1993; F-91-4-0-0-69 (Archival box - standard 91-16)
  - Saywell's farewell party, 1993; F-91-4-0-0-70 (Archival box - standard 91-16)
  - Twenty-five year employee reception, 1993; F-91-4-0-0-71 (Archival box - standard 91-16)
  - Simon Fraser University Pipe Band, 1993 - 1994; F-91-4-0-0-72 (Archival box - standard 91-16)
  - Dean's reception - certificate and diploma ceremony, 1994; F-91-4-0-0-73 (Archival box - standard 91-16)
  - Thelma Finlyason Society reception, 1994; F-91-4-0-0-74 (Archival box - standard 91-16)
  - Miscellaneous events, 1994; F-91-4-0-0-75 (Archival box - standard 91-16)
  - Faculty and staff retirement reception, 1994; F-91-4-0-0-76 (Archival box - standard 91-16)
  - Convocation -Secwepemc Cultural Education Centre, Kamloops, 1994; F-91-4-0-0-77 (Archival box - standard 91-16)
  - Twenty-five year employee reception, 1994; F-91-4-0-0-78 (Archival box - standard 91-16)
  - Convocation - University College of the Cariboo, 1994; F-91-4-0-0-79 (Archival box - standard 91-16)
  - Convocation - University College of the Fraser Valley, 1994; F-91-4-0-0-80 (Archival box - standard 91-16)
  - Correspondence—Donna Laws, 1982 - 1992; F-91-4-0-0-81 (Archival box - standard 91-16)
  - Gala dinner to honour Dr. Gordon Shrum, vol. 1, 19 November 1983; F-91-4-0-0-82 (Archival box - small 91-26)
  - Gala dinner to honour Dr. Gordon Shrum, vol. 2, 19 November 1983; F-91-4-0-0-83 (Archival box - small 91-26)
  - Historical postcards, 1965 - 1980; F-91-4-0-0-84 (Cassette box 91-27)
  - Simon Fraser University Song, [196-?]; F-91-4-0-0-85
- Awards ceremony files, 1983 - 1994; F-91-5; 25 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to the production of the annual Awards Ceremony and the Honour Roll Reception. Records include programs, books of words correspondence, publications, advisory committee minutes and other documents.
  - Awards Ceremony, 1983; F-91-5-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 91-17)
  - Awards Ceremony, 1984; F-91-5-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 91-17)
  - Awards Ceremony, 1985; F-91-5-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 91-17)
  - Awards Ceremony - Advisory committee, 1985 - 1986; F-91-5-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 91-17)
  - Awards Ceremony, 1986; F-91-5-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 91-17)
  - Awards Ceremony - Advisory committee, 1986 - 1987; F-91-5-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 91-17)
  - Awards Ceremony, 1987; F-91-5-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 91-17)
  - Awards Ceremony - Advisory committee, 1987 - 1988; F-91-5-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 91-17)
  - Awards Ceremony, 1988; F-91-5-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 91-17)
  - Honour Roll Reception, 1988; F-91-5-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 91-17)
  - Awards Ceremony - Advisory committee, 1988 - 1989; F-91-5-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 91-18)
  - Awards Ceremony, 1989; F-91-5-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 91-18)
  - Honour Roll Reception, 1989; F-91-5-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 91-18)
  - Awards Ceremony, 1990; F-91-5-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 91-18)
  - Honour Roll Reception, 1990; F-91-5-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 91-18)
  - Awards Ceremony, 1991; F-91-5-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 91-18)
  - Honour Roll Reception, 1991; F-91-5-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 91-18)
  - Awards Ceremony, 1992; F-91-5-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 91-18)
  - Honour Roll Reception, 1992; F-91-5-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 91-18)
  - Awards Ceremony, 1993; F-91-5-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 91-18)
  - Awards Ceremony - Advisory committee, 1993; F-91-5-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 91-18)
  - Honour Roll Reception, 1993; F-91-5-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 91-18)
  - Honour Roll Reception, 1993; F-91-5-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 91-18)
  - Awards Ceremony, 1994; F-91-5-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 91-18)
  - Honour Roll Reception, 1994; F-91-5-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 91-18)
- Openings and dedication--Burnaby files, 1982 - 1994; F-91-6; 18 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to the opening, naming and dedication of buildings and facilities at the Burnaby campus, and the openings of the Faculties of Business Administration and Engineering Science. Records include invitations, guest lists, programs, books of words (order of proceedings), correspondence, news releases, publications, photographs, and other documents.
  Photographic materials
  - Bennett Library naming; dedication of Shrum Science Centre, 1982; F-91-6-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 91-19)
  - Ceremony to name Klaus Rieckhoff Hall, 1982; F-91-6-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 91-19)
  - Convocation - to inaugurate the Faculty of Business Administration, 1982; F-91-6-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 91-19)
  - Jack and Sadie Diamond University Club dedication dinner, 1982; F-91-6-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 91-19)
  - Official opening ceremony - Faculty of Engineering Science, 1984; F-91-6-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 91-19)
  - Margaret and Patrick McTaggart-Cowan Hall dedication, 1986; F-91-6-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 91-19)
  - Terry Fox Field dedication, 1986; F-91-6-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 91-19)
  - Frank Allison Linville Hall dedication, 1987; F-91-6-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 91-19)
  - E.R. Loftus and C.B. Riley dedication ceremony, 1987; F-91-6-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 91-19)
  - George and Ida Halpern Centre official opening, 1989; F-91-6-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 91-19)
  - Applied Sciences Building official opening, 1990; F-91-6-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 91-19)
  - Jack and Sadie Diamond Building dedication, 1992; F-91-6-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 91-19)
    Textual records; Photographic materials
  - Earl and Jennie Lohn Business Centre sod turning ceremony, 1992; F-91-6-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 91-20)
  - William and Ruth Hamilton Hall dedication, 1992; F-91-6-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 91-20)
  - Earl and Jennie Lohn Building dedication, 1992 - 1994; F-91-6-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 91-20)
  - South Science Building official opening ceremony, 1993; F-91-6-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 91-20)
  - Gordon M. Shrum Chair reception; Centre for Experimental and Constructive Mathematics opening, 1993; F-91-6-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 91-20)
  - Jack and Sadie Diamond Building opening, 1994; F-91-6-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 91-20)
  - David See-Chai Lam Graduate Research Centre opening, 1994; F-91-6-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 91-20)
- Openings and dedication--Harbour Centre files, 1988 - 1995; F-91-7; 36 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to the opening of the Harbour Centre Campus. Activities documented include the planning and production of the official opening ceremonies, celebration dinner, faculty and staff reception, and public open house, as well as the openings, dedications, and namings of individual rooms and facilities within Harbour Centre. Records include invitations, guest lists, programs, books of words (order of proceedings), correspondence, news releases, publications, briefing notes, photographs, and other documents.
  - Harbour Centre Opening - general information, 1988 - 1989; F-91-7-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 91-20)
  - Harbour Centre Opening - planning, 1988 - 1989; F-91-7-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 91-20)
  - Harbour Centre Opening - correspondence, 1988 - 1989; F-91-7-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 91-20)
  - Harbour Centre Opening - invitations, 1989; F-91-7-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 91-20)
  - Harbour Centre Opening - program, 1988 - 1989; F-91-7-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 91-20)
  - Harbour Centre official opening ceremony, 1988 - 1989; F-91-7-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 91-20)
  - Alan and Margaret Eyre Board Room reception, 1988 - 1989; F-91-7-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 91-20)
  - BCE Development Lecture Room, 1988 - 1989; F-91-7-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 91-20)
  - Canfor Policy Room, 1988 - 1989; F-91-7-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 91-21)
  - E.J. Safarik, Sr. Conference Room, 1988 - 1989; F-91-7-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 91-21)
  - Harbour Centre celebration dinner, 1989; F-91-7-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 91-21)
  - Dedication - CIBC Lecture Room, 1989; F-91-7-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 91-21)
  - Cominco Policy Room, 1988 - 1989; F-91-7-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 91-21)
  - Diamond Alumni Centre, 1989; F-91-7-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 91-21)
  - Bentall Lecture Room, 1989; F-91-7-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 91-21)
  - Fletcher Challenge Theatre dedication, 1989; F-91-7-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 91-21)
  - IBM Interaction Lab, 1989; F-91-7-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 91-21)
  - Joseph and Rosalie Segal Centre, 1989; F-91-7-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 91-21)
  - Paperboard Industries Language Lab, 1989; F-91-7-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 91-21)
  - Pemberton Securities Meeting Room, 1989; F-91-7-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 91-21)
  - Placer Dome Lecture Room, 1989; F-91-7-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 91-21)
  - Harbour Centre Opening reception, 1989; F-91-7-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 91-21)
  - Repap Policy Room dedication, 1989; F-91-7-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 91-21)
  - Royal Bank Computing Centre, 1989; F-91-7-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 91-21)
  - Russell and DuMoulin Seminar Room, 1989; F-91-7-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 91-21)
  - Samuel and Frances Belzberg Library, 1989; F-91-7-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 91-21)
  - ScotiaMcLeod Conference Room, 1989; F-91-7-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 91-21)
  - Scotiabank Lecture Room, 1989; F-91-7-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 91-22)
  - Teck Gallery Lounge, 1989; F-91-7-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 91-22)
    Access review (Jun 6, 2022) – File is open, no restricted information identified.
  - Tree Island Industries Conference Room, 1989; F-91-7-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 91-22)
  - Weldwood of Canada Limited plaque unveiling, 1989; F-91-7-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 91-22)
  - Westcoast Energy Executive Meeting Room, 1989; F-91-7-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 91-22)
  - Xerox Conference Room, 1989; F-91-7-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 91-22)
  - BC Gas Trans Mountain Pipe Line Cinema, 1990; F-91-7-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 91-22)
  - Harbour Centre Room dedications and naming ceremonies - general, 1989 - 1990; F-91-7-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 91-22)
  - Labatt Hall, 1989 - 1990; F-91-7-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 91-22)
  - David Lam Centre for International Communication, 1989 - 1990; F-91-7-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 91-22)
  - Madge Hogarth Trumbull Reading Room, 1989 - 1990; F-91-7-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 91-22)
  - Seaboard Life Seminar Room, 1989 - 1990; F-91-7-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 91-22)
  - McCarthy Tetrault Lecture Room, 1990; F-91-7-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 91-22)
  - Microsoft Canada Inc. - plaque unveiling, 1990; F-91-7-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 91-22)
  - BC Sugar - donation of piano, 1989 - 1990; F-91-7-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 91-22)
  - Brenda and David McLean Management Studies Lab, 1992; F-91-7-0-0-43 (Archival box - standard 91-22)
  - David See-Chai Lam Centre of International Communication official opening, 1992; F-91-7-0-0-44 (Archival box - standard 91-22)
  - Tenth Anniversary celebration and official opening of the new offices of the Gerontology Research Centre, 1992; F-91-7-0-0-45 (Archival box - standard 91-22)
  - Grosvernor International Conference Room, 1992; F-91-7-0-0-46 (Archival box - standard 91-22)
  - Hemlock Printers Seminar Room, 1992; F-91-7-0-0-47 (Archival box - standard 91-22)
  - Himie Koshevoy Publishing Lab, 1992; F-91-7-0-0-48 (Archival box - standard 91-22)
  - Laurentian Group Conference Room, 1992; F-91-7-0-0-49 (Archival box - standard 91-23)
  - Hy Aisenstat Contemporary Arts Studio, 1992 - 1993; F-91-7-0-0-50 (Archival box - standard 91-23)
  - Geraldine and Tong Louie Human Performance Centre, 1993; F-91-7-0-0-51 (Archival box - standard 91-23)
  - Reader's Digest Foundation of Canada Conference Room, 1995; F-91-7-0-0-52 (Archival box - standard 91-23)
  - AXA Pacific Conference Room, 1995; F-91-7-0-0-53 (Archival box - standard 91-23)
- Anniversaries files, 1975 - 1990; F-91-8; 8 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to the celebration of SFU's 10th, 20th and 25th anniversaries. Activities documented include receptions, dinners, and a Convocation Mall celebration. Records include guest lists, invitations, programs, memorabilia, correspondence, proposals, publications, and other documents.
  - Tenth Anniversary brochure, 1975; F-91-8-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 91-23)
  - Twentieth Anniversary Committee, 1984 - 1985; F-91-8-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 91-23)
  - Twentieth Anniversary Convocation Founders' dinner, vol. 1, 1985; F-91-8-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 91-23)
  - Twentieth Anniversary Convocation Founders' dinner, vol. 2, 1985; F-91-8-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 91-23)
  - Twentieth Anniversary reception for charter faculty and staff, 1985; F-91-8-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 91-23)
  - Twentieth Anniversary reception and dinner, 1985; F-91-8-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 91-23)
  - Twenty-fifth Anniversary - miscellaneous, 1989 - 1990; F-91-8-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 91-23)
  - Twenty-fifth Anniversary - publications and memorabilia, 1990; F-91-8-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 91-23)
  - Twenty-fifth Anniversary dinner, 1990; F-91-8-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 91-23)
  - Twenty-fifth Anniversary - Voyage of Discovery (school curriculum), 1990; F-91-8-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 91-23)
- Artifacts, 2005; F-91-9; 4 items
  Series consists of four banners used during SFU's fourtieth anniversary celebrations.
  The arrangement was provided by the archivist.
  Banners were received from the Ceremonies Office in 2007.
  The records are open with no restrictions.
  Item lists are available.
  - Fourtieth Anniversary Banner, vinyl, 2005; F-91-9-0-0-0-1
    Artefacts
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-91-item1.
  - Fourtieth Anniversary Banner, vinyl, 2005; F-91-9-0-0-0-2
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-91-item2.
  - Fourtieth Anniversary Banner, cloth, 2005; F-91-9-0-0-0-3
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-91-item3.
  - Fourtieth Anniversary Banner, cloth, 2005; F-91-9-0-0-0-4
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-91-item4.